<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A docker services company</title>
    <link>www.openb.net/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A docker services company</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 18:18:27 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="www.openb.net/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Problem</title>
      <link>www.openb.net/the-problem/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 18:18:27 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.openb.net/the-problem/</guid>
      <description>The problem. As a IT Solutions vendor, I need my own branded products that are low cost to deploy in order to make any money!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>our solution</title>
      <link>www.openb.net/our-solution/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 18:21:16 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.openb.net/our-solution/</guid>
      <description>OpenB.Net Platform as a Service - Your very own Cloud Infrastructure a docker based infrastructure management system that’s easy to use. OpenB.net provides a full set of infrastructure services for containers, including networking, storage services, host management, load balancing and more. these services work across any infrastructure, and make it simple to reliably deploy and manage applications.   Happier devs. Happier ops. DevOps teams are often the first group that implement openb within an organization.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Application Library</title>
      <link>www.openb.net/application-library/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 19:20:29 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>www.openb.net/application-library/</guid>
      <description>SaaS producTS. Your verY oWn cloud buSIneSS applIcatIonS Store. We rebrand beSt-In-claSS buSIneSS applIcatIonS WIth the rIGht lIcenSeS and Make theM YourS to Sell, avaIlable to launch In a feW clIckS.  
SaaS producTS. the beSt-In-claSS productS avaIlable for WhItelabelInG. cLick Here to broWSe froM our lIbrarY of pre-buIltInteGratIonS and proprIetarY add-onSthat Your coMpetItorS have no acceSS to.  the best opensource erp system digital marketing automation Slack-like enterprise chat system Kaizen workflow management Your private dropbox/google drive   $150/application monthly $100/application monthly $100/application monthly $100/application monthly $400/application monthly    cMS website visualisation dashboard project management platform Your own trello.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>